

Pablo Uboldi

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | AEROSPACE ENGINEER

I am a professional software developer with experience working in Python, Django, Flask, HTML, CSS/Bootstrap, React, and TypeScript. I am a fast learner and a self-taught person - my previous job experiences have driven me to learn diverse specialized software, such as Mathematica, SolidWorks, AutoCAD, Simscale or Matlab.

EDUCATION

- Aerospace Engineer
 National Technology University, 2021
- Electronic and Electromechanics
 Technician

Philips Argentina Technology Institute, 2007

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Personal Website (06/2022 06/2022)
- To-do list Website (05/2022 05/2022)
- Football Statistics Website (07/2022 08/2022)
- Breakout Game (04/2022 04/2022)

LANGUAGES

- · Spanish Native
- English Proficient

CONTACT



pabloauboldi@gmail.com



+44 07 5020 58637



github.com/pablouboldi

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software Engineer

July 2022 - present

- Integration of social and cryptocurrency profiles for analysis.
- O Development of a Discord Bot to collect user data.
- Web UX development for impact measurement in digital marketing campaigns, for a startup.
- Development of a Python script for solving Taylor-Maccoll equations for supersonic flow around a cone. For university use.

Fluid Mechanics Associate Professor

National Technology University, March 2018 - Present

- I oversee the theoretical and practical evaluation activities developed for the students of Aerospace Engineering.
- O Class dictation.

Project Manager

Natural and Exact Sciences Faculty, UBA, March 2014 - August 2021

- I was part of the Technical Department, co-leading the electrical maintenance team for small and medium scale projects.
- I collaborated with the IT Department in software support and troubleshooting of staff's PCs.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Football

Paddle

Videogames